So friends, we have arrived at the second week of the Real season.
This week, you will see a total of 130
companies disclosing their quarter three numbers.
So let us see which
company will be disclosing its quarterly numbers on which date.
Remember, this week is going to be a
very important week
because in this week
you will see the numbers of many companies of Nifty 50 coming.
So, this week is going to be very
important.  of this entire
Q3 results season.  Numbers of 17 companies will
come on Monday.  Let's look at some familiar names.
Anant Rathi is done, HCLT is done,
you will see TCS numbers coming on Monday.  There
are some more names.  GTPL is done,
Gujarat Hotel is done.  You will see all these names.
Remember,
this time you should
not have high expectations from any IT company on quarterly basis.  Because on a
quarterly basis, you also know that
due to Trump tariffs, India
's business with the US has slowed down a bit.
Due to which, the business of all the IT companies has been
slightly affected on a quarterly basis.  So that's why
I am telling you according to the report I have.
You should not rely too much on quarterly basis.
You can see both the revenue and profit of the company with a 2% up and down.
So
this time
you will not get to see much of the IT company numbers on a quarterly basis.
Only flat you can understand.   Let's
talk about Tuesday.
You will see the numbers of 23 companies coming on Tuesday.
Let's see some familiar names.
5 Paisa Capital, ICIC LBRD, ICICI
Pidencal, Jal, Maharashtra Bank and if you
look at them,
you will see all these names
coming on Tuesday.  Talking about Wednesday,
you will see the numbers of 22 companies coming on Wednesday.
See some familiar names.  Dead
Network HDB Finance HDFC AMC Infosys
I have already told you about the IT company and
how the numbers can come.  You will see names like MRPL
Go, ICIC AMC, IOB i.e. Indian Overseas
Bank Network 18.
However, the level of SIP is
still seen going to record levels.
So in such a situation the
AMC company should benefit.
Only after the company's results are out will it be known
whether they have made a profit or not.
But there is a high hope that all these companies will
see profits.
Talking about Grow, I will
compare Grow with Jel One and tell you what will happen.   Let's
look at Union Bank together.
You will also see the numbers of Union Bank coming on Wednesday.
Talking about Thursday,
if you look here on Thursday,
you will also see the numbers of Jel One coming.
Grow numbers will come on Wednesday and
when the business update of Jel One One came on Thursday, the company had
mentioned one thing which you must have seen that on
year after year basis, the
number of clients of the company has been
added by the company by around 2%
but where was the problem coming, the
problem was coming in the number of daily
average volume of the company because it
seems that the daily orders of the company have reduced
this time, that is, they are reducing every time.   It has been
decreasing for the last few quarters.
This time too you may see less of them.  So if
you are increasing your customers and your orders are decreasing
then this is negative because
how does your business run?  Your business
runs only when the company i.e. the client
places orders.  Your brokerage is based on that.
So because of that
you also see a decline in the share.  Due to this, there
may be a decline in profits
also.  Revenue may also fall slightly.  could be possible.
So we will have to
see how the numbers of Go jail one will come.  Along with this,
you will see all the names like 361 Delta Corp, Jio Finance, LTTS H, Hathway Cable, AOK Industries and HDFC Lab.  If we
talk about it together,
you will also see the names of HW Solar and South Indian Bank.  Let's
talk about Friday.
You will see the numbers of 30 companies coming on Friday.  But
before that I would like to tell you one thing.
I have market estimate reports of about 300 to 400 companies.  That means,
you should understand that after 1 month i.e.
around 10th February, mostly you get the
Hindustan Attic numbers.  So
today I can tell you what India's revenues can be and how much profit it can make.
Meaning, you should understand that I have
all the reports as to which company
's numbers you can see coming.  The
result season has
not even started yet.  You will see the result season starting from this week.
In my group,
which is basically a paid group,
more than 150 people have already joined it.  So you
can also join that group.  Next
I will tell you how you can join that group.
Numbers of 30 companies will come on Friday.  If we look at Central Bank
Jindals Ltd i.e. NAT Finance HCL, HHCL, HH
Specialty Chemicals, JSW Infra,
Federal Bank together, then Polc,
Pval Fincorp, Reliance Industries and together we
look at Tata Tech, Tech Mahindra and
Wipro, meaning you should understand that
after the market closes on Friday,
you may see a big reversal on Monday.
Why might a reversal be seen?  Because
when the market opens on Monday, after Friday's
closing, results of about seven to eight companies of Nifty 50 are going to come.
Mostly, the
poly numbers are released during the market hours after the market closes on Friday.
But sometimes they
come even after the market closes.  So you take Polyb.
Reliance numbers will
come after the market closes.  Tata Tech's numbers will come
after the market closes, Tech Mahindra's and
Wipro's numbers will also
come after the market closes.  And also when you
come on Saturday, you get to see two or three more big names on Saturday as well.
Because here also numbers of 12 companies will appear.
Can Finance, HDFC Bank, ICICI Bank,
Network Technology, Yes Bank and DC Biote,
so you can understand that
after the market closes on Friday, you will see the numbers of about 7 to 8 NFT 50
companies coming.
So it will be interesting to
see how the market reacts on
Monday.  Talking about Sunday,
you will not see the numbers of any company coming on Sunday.
So
friends, you have seen the result list
but the real money is made when you
know the market expectations before the results are out.
Like every time, this time
also one of our memberships has opened for the Q3 result season regarding the company's numbers.
Our WhatsApp group has been opened.  Where you get
market estimate report, that too daily in the morning
before the results are announced.  This
is the only group in India where you will get market
estimate report.  That too by paying just ₹299.  The
charges are just ₹299 for the entire Q3
result season which will last till 15th February.
So come join us
in this group.  The
link to the group is given in the comment box and description of the video.
You can join from there.  If you do
not want to blindly trade at the time of results
and want to take data driven decisions, then
definitely join the group
because for just ₹9 ₹299
you will get a lot of information on the
basis of which you can take a good decision.
And yes, you do
not need to make any payment right now.  Only the link of the group
which has been told to you is
given in the description and comment box.
You just have to join it right now.
You should join that group.  You do
n't need to make any payment anywhere else.  If
you join that group,
you will be told our UPI ID in that group.
You can join our paid group by making payment on that UPI ID.  So,
you don't need to pay anywhere else.  There
is no need to take YouTube membership.  Just do one
thing right now.  Join the group whose link has been
given
and then go there and make the payment, then you will
join the paid group.